<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<UrlPagerDoc>
  <Class name="UrlPager">
    <summary>
      Custom paging control for asp.net webform application, It supports url routing and paging through url parameter.
    </summary>
  </Class>
  <Class name="RouteValuesExpressionBuilder">
    <summary>
      Retrieves the route values that corresponds to a specified URL parameter in a routed page.
    </summary>
  </Class>
  <Property name="RouteName">
    <summary>
      Gets or sets the name of the route that is used to generate paging urls.
    </summary>
  </Property>
  <Property name="ContainerTag">
    <summary>
      Gets or sets the HTML tag name for the container element of the pager.
    </summary>
  </Property>
  <Property name="RouteValues">
    <summary>
      The route values to be applied to the route.
    </summary>
  </Property>
  <Property name="InheritsRouteValues">
    <summary>
      Gets or sets a value indicating whether UrlPager should inherit the route values from the current http context.
    </summary>
  </Property>
  <Property name="TotalItemCount">
    <summary>
      Gets or sets the total number of records that are available for paging.
    </summary>
  </Property>
  <Property name="PageSize">
    <summary>
      Gets or sets the number of records that are displayed for each page of data.
    </summary>
  </Property>
  <Property name="AutoHide">
    <summary>
      Gets or sets a value indicating whether UrlPager should be hidden if there's only one page of data.
    </summary>
  </Property>
  <Property name="PageIndexParameterName">
    <summary>
      Gets or sets the page index parameter name in the current route.
    </summary>
  </Property>
  <Property name="PageNumberFormatString">
    <summary>
      Gets or sets the format string for all numeric pager items.
    </summary>
  </Property>
  <Property name="PagerItemTemplate">
    <summary>
      Gets or sets the html template to be applied to all pager items.
    </summary>
  </Property>
  <Property name="CurrentPageNumberFormatString">
    <summary>
      Gets or sets the format string for the current page number.
    </summary>
  </Property>
  <Property name="NumericPagerItemTemplate">
    <summary>
      Gets or sets the html template for the numeric pager items.
    </summary>
  </Property>
  <Property name="CurrentPagerItemTemplate">
    <summary>
      Gets or sets the html template to be applied to the current page pager item.
    </summary>
  </Property>
  <Property name="NavigationPagerItemTemplate">
    <summary>
      Gets or sets the html template to be applied to the first, previous, next and last page pager items.
    </summary>
  </Property>
  <Property name="DisabledPagerItemTemplate">
    <summary>
      Gets or sets the html template to be applied to the disabled pager items.
    </summary>
  </Property>
  <Property name="MorePagerItemTemplate">
    <summary>
      Gets or sets the html template to be applied to the more pager items.
    </summary>
  </Property>
  <Property name="AlwaysShowFirstLastPageNumber">
    <summary>
      Gets or sets a value indicating whether the first and the last numeric pager items should be displaye.
    </summary>
  </Property>
  <Property name="NumericPagerItemCount">
    <summary>
      Gets or sets the maximum number of the numeric pager items to be displayed.
    </summary>
  </Property>
  <Property name="ShowPrevNext">
    <summary>
      Gets or sets a value indicating whether the previous page and the next page pager items should be displayed.
    </summary>
  </Property>
  <Property name="PrevPageText">
    <summary>
      Gets or sets the text displayed for the previous page pager item.
    </summary>
  </Property>
  <Property name="NextPageText">
    <summary>
      Gets or sets the text displayed for the next page pager item.
    </summary>
  </Property>
  <Property name="ShowNumericPagerItems">
    <summary>
      Gets or sets a value indicating whether the numeric pager items should be displayed.
    </summary>
  </Property>
  <Property name="ShowFirstLast">
    <summary>
      Gets or sets a value indicating whether the first page and the last page pager items should be displayed.
    </summary>
  </Property>
  <Property name="FirstPageText">
    <summary>
      Gets or sets the text displayed for the first page button.
    </summary>
  </Property>
  <Property name="LastPageText">
    <summary>
      Gets or sets the text displayed for the last page pager item.
    </summary>
  </Property>
  <Property name="ShowMorePagerItems">
    <summary>
      Gets or sets a value indicating whether the more pager items should be displayed.
    </summary>
  </Property>
  <Property name="MorePageText">
    <summary>
      Gets or sets the text displayed for the more pager items.
    </summary>
  </Property>
  <Property name="ShowDisabledPagerItems">
    <summary>
      Gets or sets a value indicating whether the disabled pager items should be displayed.
    </summary>
  </Property>
  <Property name="ReversePageIndex">
    <summary>
      Gets or sets a value indicating whether page index in the url should be reversed, that means the last page index will be 1 while the current page index is the total page number.
    </summary>
  </Property>
  <Property name="CurrentPageIndex">
    <summary>
      Gets or sets the current page index.
    </summary>
  </Property>
  <Property name="StartItemIndex">
    <summary>
      Gets the index of the first data item that is displayed on the current page.
    </summary>
  </Property>
  <Property name="EndItemIndex">
    <summary>
      Gets the index of the last data item that is displayed on the current page.
    </summary>
  </Property>
  <Property name="TotalPageCount">
    <summary>
      Gets the total number of pages.
    </summary>
  </Property>
  <Method name="OnPageChanged">
    <summary>
      Raises the PageChanged event.
    </summary>
  </Method>
  <Event name="PageChanged">
    <summary>
      Occurs when one of the pager buttons is clicked, but after the control handles the paging operation.
    </summary>
  </Event>
</UrlPagerDoc>